{
	"q1":{
		"question":"Which Premiership football club plays its home games at White Hart Lane?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Arsenal",
			"B":"Chelsea",
			"C":"Tottenham Hotspur",
			"D":"West Ham United"
		},
		"answer":"C",
		"time":5
	},
	"q2":{
		"question":"Who was England's chief coach at the 2006 FIFA World Cup ?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Arsene Wenger",
			"B":"Glen Hoddle",
			"C":"kevin Keegan",
			"D":"Sven Goran Hogson"
		},
		"answer":"D",
		"time":5
	},
	"q3":{
		"question":"Which English footballer scored a great goal against Argentina in the 1998 World Cup?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Glenn Hoddle",
			"B":"Ian Wright",
			"C":"Les Ferdinand",
			"D":"Michael Owen"

		},
		"answer":"D",
		"time":5
	},
	"q4":{
		"question":"What are Bristol's two football clubs called?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Athletic and City",
			"B":"City and Rovers",
			"C":"Rovers and United",
			"D":"United and Wanderers"
		},
		"answer":"B",
		"time":5
	},
	"q5":{
		"question":"What colour are the home shirts of Everton Football Club?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Blue",
			"B":"Green and White Hoops",
			"C":"Red",
			"D":"Yellow and Black"
		},
		"answer":"A",
		"time":5
	},
	"q6":{
		"question":"Which country did footballer Kenny Dalglish represent?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Ireland",
			"B":"Scotland",
			"C":"wales",
			"D":"English"
		},
		"answer":"B",
		"time":5
	},
	"q7":{
		"question":"Which country won its fifth football World Cup in 2002?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Brazil",
			"B":"Germany",
			"C":"Italy",
			"D":"Uruguay"
		},
		"answer":"A",
		"time":5
	},
	"q8":{
		"question":"Which of these football clubs is not based in Lancashire?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Barnsley",
			"B":"Blackburn Rovers",
			"C":"Him",
			"D":"Her"
		},
		"answer":"A",
		"time":5
	},
	"q9":{
		"question":"'The Wizard Of Dribble', which Stanley was a famous England footballer?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Baldwin",
			"B":"Halloway",
			"C":"Laurel",
			"D":"Mathews"
		},
		"answer":"D",
		"time":5
	},
	"q10":{
		"question":"Which footballer was known as 'Gazza'?",
		"choices":{
			"A":"Garry Lineker",
			"B":"Gary Mabutt",
			"C":"Gary Speed",
			"D":"Paul Gasgoine"
		},
		"answer":"D",
		"time":5
	}
}